<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<event>
    <name>Retrace Server</name>
    <description>Send core dump to remote retrace server for analysis</description>
    <description xml:lang="as">বিশ্লেষণৰ বাবে দূৰৱৰ্তী ৰিট্ৰেইচ চাৰ্ভাৰলে কৌৰ ডাম্প পঠাওক</description>
    <description xml:lang="bg">Изпращане съдържанието на паметта на отдалечен анализиращ сървър</description>
    <description xml:lang="bn">বিশ্লেষণের জন্য retrace সার্ভারের মধ্যে কোর-ডাম্প পাঠানো হয়</description>
    <description xml:lang="bn_IN">বিশ্লেষণের জন্য retrace সার্ভারের মধ্যে কোর-ডাম্প পাঠানো হয়</description>
    <description xml:lang="bs">Pošalji ispis jezgre na udaljeni retrace server za analizu</description>
    <description xml:lang="ca">Envia el bolc de la memòria al servidor remot de retraçat per a l'anàlisi</description>
    <description xml:lang="cs">Odešle obraz paměti k analýze na vzdálený retrace server</description>
    <description xml:lang="da">Send kernedump til fjern-retraceserver for analysering</description>
    <description xml:lang="de">Speicherauszug an entfernten Server zur Untersuchung senden</description>
    <description xml:lang="el">Στείλε αναφορά σφάλματος στον απομακρυσμένο εξηπηρετητή για ανάλυση</description>
    <description xml:lang="en_GB">Send core dump to remote retrace server for analysis</description>
    <description xml:lang="es">Enviar volcado de memoria al servidor retrace remoto para su análisis</description>
    <description xml:lang="et">Saada tuuma tõmmis teise taasjälituse serverisse analüüsimiseks</description>
    <description xml:lang="fi">Lähetä muistivedos etäpalvelimelle analysointavaksi</description>
    <description xml:lang="fr">Envoyer la trace mémoire au serveur retrace pour analyse</description>
    <description xml:lang="gu">વિશ્ર્લેષણ માટે દૂરસ્થ રિટ્રેસ સર્વરમાં કોર ડમ્પને મોકલો</description>
    <description xml:lang="he">שליחת מידע לשרת מעקב־מחדש מרוחק לניתוח</description>
    <description xml:lang="hi">विश्लेषण के लिए दूरस्थ रिट्रेस सर्वर में कोर डंप भेजें</description>
    <description xml:lang="hu">Az összeomlási adatok elküldése a nyomkövetési kiszolgálónak további elemzésre</description>
    <description xml:lang="ia">Inviar le instantaneo del memoria al servitor de retraciamento pro analyse</description>
    <description xml:lang="id">Kirim core dump untuk retrace remote server untuk analisis</description>
    <description xml:lang="it">Invia il core dump sul retrace server remoto per l'analisi</description>
    <description xml:lang="ja">コアダンプを分析のためリモートのリトレースサーバーに送信します</description>
    <description xml:lang="kn">ಕೋರ್ ಡಂಪ್ ಅನ್ನು ವಿಶ್ಲೇಷಣೆಗಾಗಿ ದೂರಸ್ಥ ರಿಟ್ರೇಸ್ ಪೂರೈಕೆಗಣಕಕ್ಕೆ ಕಳುಹಿಸು</description>
    <description xml:lang="ko">분석을 위해 코어 덤프를 원격 Retrace 서버로 전송 </description>
    <description xml:lang="lt">Siųsti pagrindo išklotinę į nutolusį serverį analizei</description>
    <description xml:lang="ml">നിരീക്ഷിയ്ക്കുന്നതിനായി റിമോട്ട് റീട്രെയിസ് സര്‍വറിലേക്കു് കോര്‍ ഡംപ് അയയ്ക്കുക</description>
    <description xml:lang="mr">विश्लेषणकरीता कोर डम्पला रिट्रेस सर्व्हरकरीता पाठवा</description>
    <description xml:lang="nl">Stuur coredump naar retrace-server op afstand voor analyse</description>
    <description xml:lang="or">ସୁଦୂର ଅନୁସନ୍ଧାନ ସର୍ଭର ପାଖକୁ ବିଶ୍ଳେଷଣ ପାଇଁ କୋରଡମ୍ପ ପଠାନ୍ତୁ</description>
    <description xml:lang="pa">ਜਾਂਚ ਵਾਸਤੇ ਕੋਰਡੰਪ ਨੂੰ ਰਿਮੋਟ ਰੀਟਰੇਸ ਸਰਵਰ ਉੱਪਰ ਭੇਜੋ</description>
    <description xml:lang="pl">Wysyła zrzut core do zdalnego serwera ponownego śledzenia do analizy</description>
    <description xml:lang="pt">Enviar core dump para o servidor retrace remoto para análise</description>
    <description xml:lang="pt_BR">Envia o despejo de núcleo ao servidor de retraçamento remoto para análise</description>
    <description xml:lang="ru">Отправка дампа памяти удалённому серверу для анализа</description>
    <description xml:lang="sk">Odoslať výpis jadra na analýzu na vzdialený retrace server</description>
    <description xml:lang="sq">Dërgo core dump në serverin e largët retrace për analizim</description>
    <description xml:lang="sr">Пошаљи coredump на удаљени сервер за поновни траг на анализу</description>
    <description xml:lang="sv">Skickar minnesdump till fjärrspårningsserver för analys</description>
    <description xml:lang="ta">சோதனைக்காக தொலை மறுதடமறிதல் சேவையகத்தை கோர் டம்ப்பிற்காக அனுப்பவும்</description>
    <description xml:lang="te">విశ్లేషణ కొరకు కోర్ డంప్‌ను రిమోట్ రీట్రేస్ సర్వర్‌కు పంపుము</description>
    <description xml:lang="tr">Bellek dökümünü incelemek için uzak retrace sunucusuna gönder</description>
    <description xml:lang="uk">Надіслати дамп ядра на сервер повторного трасування для аналізу</description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_CN">发送核心转储至远程追溯服务器以供分析</description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_TW">傳送核心傾印至遠端追溯伺服器來分析</description>
    <long-description>Uploads coredump to a server, which generates backtrace and returns it. Pros: no need for debuginfo downloads. Retrace server's database of debuginfos is more complete. Retrace server may generate better backtraces. Cons: coredump you upload contains all the data from the crashed program, including your private data, if any.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="as">কৌৰডাম্পক এটা চাৰ্ভাৰলে আপলোড কৰে, যি বেকট্ৰেইচ সৃজন কৰে আৰু ইয়াক পঠায়। সুবিধা: debuginfo ডাউনলোডসমূহৰ প্ৰয়োজন নাই। debuginfos -ৰ চাৰ্ভাৰৰ ডাটাবেইচ ৰিট্ৰেইচ কৰা সম্পূৰ্ণ। ৰেট্ৰেইচ চাৰ্ভাৰে উন্নত বেকট্ৰেইচসমূহ সৃজন কৰিব পাৰে। অসুবিধাসমূহ: আপুনি আপলোড কৰা কৌৰডাম্পে স্খলিত প্ৰগ্ৰামৰ পৰা সকলো তথ্য অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে, আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত তথ্য অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰাকৈ, যদি কোনো আছে।</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="bg">Качва копие от паметта на сървър, който генерира обратно проследяващ анализ и го изпраща обратно. За: няма нужда от сваляне на debuginfo пакети. Базата данни на Retrace сървърите е по-пълна. Retrace сървърът може да генерира по-качествен анализ. Против: копието на паметта, което качвате, съдържа всички данни на провалилата се програма, включително, ако има, Ваши поверителни данни.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="bn">সার্ভারের মধ্যে coredump আপলোড করে এবং সার্ভারে ব্যাক-ট্রেস প্রস্তুত করে ফেরৎ দেওয়া হয়।সুবিধা: debuginfo ডাউনলোড করার প্রয়োজন নেই। রি-ট্রেস সার্ভারের ডাটাবেস অনেক বেশি পরিপূর্ণ ও সার্ভার থেকে উন্নত ব্যাক-ট্রেস প্রাপ্ত হবে।অসুবিধা: আপলোড করা coredump-র মধ্যে গোপনীয় তথ্য সহ বিপর্যস্ত প্রোগ্রামের সকল তথ্য অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়।</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="bn_IN">সার্ভারের মধ্যে coredump আপলোড করে এবং সার্ভারে ব্যাক-ট্রেস প্রস্তুত করে ফেরৎ দেওয়া হয়।সুবিধা: debuginfo ডাউনলোড করার প্রয়োজন নেই। রি-ট্রেস সার্ভারের ডাটাবেস অনেক বেশি পরিপূর্ণ ও সার্ভার থেকে উন্নত ব্যাক-ট্রেস প্রাপ্ত হবে।অসুবিধা: আপলোড করা coredump-র মধ্যে গোপনীয় তথ্য সহ বিপর্যস্ত প্রোগ্রামের সকল তথ্য অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়।</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="bs">Prebacuje ispis jezgre na server koji stvara funkcijski trag i vraća ga. Za: nema potrebe za debuginfo preuzimanjima. Retrace serverova baza podataka  debuginfo-a je potpunija. Retrace server može stvarati bolje funkcijske tragove. Protiv: ispis jezgre koji prebacite sadrži sve podatke iz srušenog programa uključujući Vaše privatne podatke (ako postoje).</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ca">Puja el bolc de la memòria a un servidor que genera una traça inversa i la retorna. Pros: no hi ha la necessitat de baixar els debuginfo. La base de dades dels debuginfo del servidor de retraçat és més completa. El servidor de retraçat pot generar millor les traces inverses. Cons: el bolc de la memòria que pugeu conté totes les dades del programa que ha tingut pana, que inclouen les vostres dades privades, si fos el cas.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="cs">Nahraje obraz paměti na server, který vytvoří výpis volání a vrátí jej. Výhody: Netřeba stahovat balíčky s ladicími údaji. Databáze retrace serveru již obsahuje většinu těchto balíčků. Retrace server může vytvořit lepší výpis volání.Nevýhody: obraz paměti, který nahrajete na server, obsahuje všechny údaje z havarovaného programu včetně soukromých údajů, byly-li přítomny.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="da">Uploader kernedump til en server, som genererer backtracet og returnerer det. Fordele: ingen behov til at downloade fejlsøgningsinfo. Retraceserverens database over fejlsøgningsinformationer er mere komplet. Retraceserveren genererer muligvis bedre backtraces. Ulemper: kernedumpninger som du uploader indeholder alle data fra det nedbrudte program, inklusiv dine private data, hvis de er tilstede.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="de">Überträgt einen Speicherauszug an einen Retrace-Server, der eine Ablaufverfolgung erstellt und zurücksendet. Die Debuginfo-Datenbank des Retrace-Servers ist in der Regel vollständiger. Dagegen spricht, dass der zu übertragende Speicherauszug alle Daten der abgestürzten Anwendung enthält, eventuell auch vertrauliche Daten.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="el">Ανεβάζει πληροφορίες σφάλματος σε εναν εξυπηρετητή, που παράγει backtrace και το επιστρέφει.
Πλεονεκτήματα: Δεν χρειάζεται κατέβασμα πληροφοριών αποσφαλμάτωσης. Η βάση δεδομένων πληροφοριών αποσφαλμάτωσης του εξυπηρετητή επανανίχνευσης ειναι πιο πλήρης. Ο εξυπηρετητής επανανίχνευσης μπορεί να φτιάξει καλύτερα backtraces.
Μειωνεκτήματα: Οι πληροφορίες σφάλματος που ανεβάζετε περιέχουν όλα τα δεδομένα του σπασμένου προγράμματος, συμπεριλαμβανομένων και των προσωπικών σας δεδομένων. </long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="en_GB">Uploads coredump to a server, which generates backtrace and returns it. Pros: no need for debuginfo downloads. Retrace server's database of debuginfos is more complete. Retrace server may generate better backtraces. Cons: coredump you upload contains all the data from the crashed program, including your private data, if any.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="es">Sube el volcado de memoria a un servidor, que generará el trazado y lo devolverá. Ventajas: no son necesarias las descargas de información de depuración. La base de datos de información de depuración del servidor Retrace es más completa. El servidor Retrace puede generar mejores trazados. Contras: el archivo de volcado que va a subir contiene todos los datos del programa que falló, incluidos datos privados si los hubiera.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="et">Laadib tuumatõmmise serverisse, mis genereerib tagasijälituse ning tagastab selle. Eelised: ei pea silumisinfo pakke alla laadima. Taasjälituse serveri silumisinfo andemebaas on täielikum. Taasjälituse server võib genereerida parema tagasijälituse. Puudused: üleslaaditav tuumatõmmis sisaldab erinevat infot, mis programmi krahhima pani, sealhulgas ka võimalikku isiklikku infot.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="fi">Lähettää muistivedoksen palvelimelle, joka luo pinolistauksen ja palauttaa sen. Hyödyt: debuginfo-tiedostoja ei tarvitse ladata. Palvelimen debuginfo-tietokanta on kattavampi. Palvelin saattaa luoda parempia pinolistauksia. Haitat: lähetettävä muistivedos sisältää kaikki kaatuneen ohjelman tiedot, myös mahdolliset yksityiset tiedot.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="fr">Téléverse le vidage du processus sur un serveur, ce qui génère une trace arrière et la renvoie. Avantages : télécharger debuginfo n’est plus nécessaire, la base de données de debuginfo du serveur Retrace est plus complète. Le serveur Retrace peut aussi générer de meilleures traces arrière. Défauts : le vidage du processus téléchargé contient toutes les données du programme en échec, y compris vos données personnelles s’il y en a.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="gu">સર્વરમાં coredump ને અપલોડ કરે છે, કે જે બેકટ્રેસને ઉત્પન્ન કરે છે અને તેને પાછુ લાવે છે. ફાયદો: debuginfo ડાઉનલોડ કરવા માટે જરૂરી નથી. debuginfos નાં રિટ્રેસ સર્વરનાં ડેટાબેઝ સમાપ્ત છે. રિટ્રેસ સર્વર એ બેકટ્રેસને સારી રીતે ઉત્પન્ન કરી શકે છે. ગેરફાયદો: coredump જે તમે ભંગાણ થયેલ કાર્યક્રમમાંથી સમાવેલ બધી માહિતીનો અપલોડ કરો છો, તમારી ખાનગી માહિતીને સમાવી રહ્યા છે, જો કોઇપણ હોય.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="he">מעלה את ה־coredump לשרת, שמייצר מידע קריסה ומחזיר אותו. יתרונות: אין צורך בהורדת חבילות מידע ניפוי שגיאות, מאגר מידע ניפוי השגיאות שלם יותר, והוא עשוי לייצר מידע שמיש יותר. חסרונות: ה־coredump שמועלה לשרת מרוחק מכיל את כל המידע מהתוכנה שקרסה, כולל מידע פרטי, אם קיים. (החיבור מוצפן, אל דאגה).</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="hi">किसी सर्वर में कोरडंप अपलोड करता है, जो बैकट्रेस जनन करता है और इसे फिर वापस करता है. पक्ष: डिबगइंफो डाउनलोड के लिए की कोई जरूरत नहीं. डिबगइंफो का रिट्रेस सर्वर डेटाबेस अधिक पूर्ण है. रिट्रेस सर्वर अधिक बैकट्रेस जनन कर सकता है. विपक्ष: आपके द्वारा अपलोड किया गया कोरडंप क्रैश किए प्रोग्राम से सभी आँकड़ों को समाहित किए है, जिसमें आपके निजी आँकड़े समाहित हैं, यदि कोई है.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="hu">Feltölti az összeomlási adatokat a kiszolgáló, amely visszakövetést készít, és visszaküldi azokat. Előnye: nincs szükség a debuginfo csomagok letöltésére, valamint a nyomkövető kiszolgáló jobb eredményekre képes a teljesebb debuginfo csomagjaival. Hátrányok: a feltöltött összeomlási adatok az összeomlott programból származnak, és így akár személyes adatokat is tartalmazhatnak.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ia">Invia le instantaneo del memoria a un servitor, le qual genera le retraciamento e lo reinvia. Avantages: non es necessari discargar debuginfo; le information debuginfo sur le servitor de retraciamento es plus complete; le servitor pote generar melior retraciamentos. Disavantages: le instantaneo del memoria que tu invia contine tote le datos del programma fallite, incluse tu datos private, si existe.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="it">Carica il coredump sul server, generando un backtrace e successivamente ritornandolo. Pro: non c'è bisogno di scaricare le informazioni di debug. Il database delle informazioni di debug sul retrace server è più completo. Il retrace server può generare backtrace migliori. Contro: il coredump da caricare contiene tutti i dati del programma, incluso dati privati quando presenti.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ja">コアダンプをサーバーにアップロードします。これによりバックトレースが生成され返されます。debuginfo をダウンロードする必要がない点が利点となります。リトレースサーバーの debaguinfo データベースの方がより完全なデータベースとなるため、リトレースサーバーの方がより適切なバックトレースを生成することができます。一方、アップロードするコアダンプにはクラッシュしたプログラムの全データが含まれるため、プライベートデータがある場合には、そのデータも含まれることになります。</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="kn">ಕೋರ್ ಡಂಪ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಪೂರೈಕೆಗಣಕಕ್ಕೆ ಅಪ್‌ಲೋಡ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ, ಇದು ಬ್ಯಾಕ್‌ಟ್ರೇಸ್‌ ಅನ್ನು ಉತ್ಪಾದಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಹಾಗು ಅದನ್ನು ಮರಳಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಅನುಕೂಲಗಳು: ದೋಷನಿವಾರಣಾಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಡೌನ್‌ಲೋಡ್ ಮಾಡುವ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ. ದೋಷನಿವಾರಣಾಮಾಹಿತಿಯ ರಿಟ್ರೇಸ್ ಪೂರೈಕೆಗಣಕದ ದತ್ತಸಂಚಯವು ಹೆಚ್ಚು ಪರಿಪೂರ್ಣವಾಗಿರುತ್ತದೆ. ರಿಟ್ರೇಸ್ ಪೂರೈಕೆಗಣಕವು ಉತ್ತಮವಾದ ಬ್ಯಾಕ್‌ಟ್ರೇಸ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಉತ್ಪಾದಿಸಬಲ್ಲದು. ಅನಾನುಕೂಲಗಳು: ನೀವು ಅಪ್‌ಲೋಡ್ ಮಾಡುವ ಕೋರ್ ಡಂಪ್ ನಿಮ್ಮ ಯಾವುದಾದರೂ ಖಾಸಗಿ ಮಾಹಿತಿ ಇದ್ದಲ್ಲಿ ಅದೂ ಸೇರಿದಂತೆ ಕುಸಿತಗೊಂಡ ಪ್ರೊಗ್ರಾಮ್‌ನ ಎಲ್ಲಾ ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಹೊಂದಿರುತ್ತದೆ.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ko">코어 덤프를 서버에 업로드하려면 백트레이스를 생성하고 이를 반환합니다. 장점: debuginfo를 다운로드할 필요가 없습니다. Retrace 서버의 debuginfo 데이터베이스는 보다 완벽합니다. Retrace 서버는 보다 나은 백트레이스를 생성합니다. 단점: 업로드한 코어 덤프에는 (존재할 경우) 개인 데이터를 포함하여 충돌된 프로그램에서의 모든 데이터가 포함되어 있습니다.      </long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="lt">Nusiunčia pagrindo išklotinę į serverį, kuris sukuria pėdsaką ir jį įvykdo. Privalumai: nereikia parsiųsti derinimo informacijos. Pertrasavimo serverio derinimo informacijos duomenų bazė yra pilnesnė. Pertrasavimo serveris gali sugeneruoti geresnius pėdsakus. Trūkumai: pagrindo išklotinės turi visus lūžusios programos duomenis, įskaitant privačius.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ml">ഒരു സര്‍വറിലേക്കു് കോര്‍ഡംപ് അപ്‌ലോഡ് ചെയ്യുന്നു, ഇതു് ബാക്ക്ട്രെയിസ് ലഭ്യമാക്കി തിരികെ ലഭ്യമാക്കുന്നു. പ്രശ്നങ്ങള്‍: debuginfo ഡൌണ്‍ലോഡുകള്‍ ആവശ്യമില്ല. റീട്രെയിസ് സര്‍വറിന്റെ debuginfo ഡേറ്റാബെയിസ് കൂടുതല്‍ പൂര്‍ണ്ണമാണു്. റീട്രെയിസ് സര്‍വര്‍ ഒരു പക്ഷേ മെച്ചപ്പെട്ട ബാക്ക്ട്രെയിസുകള്‍ ലഭ്യമാക്കുന്നു. ഫലങ്ങള്‍: നിങ്ങള്‍ അപ്‌ലോഡ് ചെയ്ത കോര്‍ഡംപില്‍ തകര്‍ന്ന പ്രോഗ്രാമിന്റെ എല്ലാ ഡേറ്റയും അടങ്ങുന്നു.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="mr">कोरडम्पला सर्व्हरकरीता अपलोड करतो, जे बॅकट्रेस निर्माण करते व पाठवते. फायदे: debuginfo डाऊनलोड्स्ची आवश्यकता नाही. रिट्रेस सर्व्हरचे डिबगइंफोचे डाटाबेस बऱ्यापैकी पूर्ण आहे. रिट्रेस सर्व्हर उत्तम बॅकट्रेसेस् निर्माण करू शकतो. तोटे: अपलोड करण्याजोगी कोरडम्पमध्ये क्रॅश्ड् प्रोग्रामपासूनचे सर्व डाटा समाविष्टीत आहे, व्यक्तिगत डाटा समाविष्टीत, आढळल्यास.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="nl">Upload een coredump naar een server, die een backtrace genereert en deze vervolgens terugstuurt. Voordelen: debuginfo downloaden is niet nodig. De database van debuginfos van de retrace-server is completer. De retrace-server kan betere backtraces genereren. Nadelen: een coredump van jouw upload bevat alle data van het gecrashte programma, mogelijk inclusief persoonlijke data.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="or">ସର୍ଭରରେ କୋରଡମ୍ପକୁ ଧାରଣ କରିଥାଏ, ଯାହାକି ବ୍ୟାକଟ୍ରେସ ସୃଷ୍ଟିକରିଥାଏ ଏବଂ ତାହାକୁ ଫେରାଇଥାଏ। ଲାଭ: ତ୍ରୁଟି ନିବାରଣ ଆହରଣର ଆବଶ୍ୟକତା ନାହିଁ। ଅନୁସନ୍ଧାନ ସର୍ଭରର ତ୍ରୁଟିନିବାରଣ ସୂଚନା ତଥ୍ୟାଧାରଟି ଅଧିକ ସମ୍ପୂର୍ଣ୍ଣ। ଅନୁସନ୍ଧାନ ସର୍ଭର ହୁଏତଃ ଉତ୍ତମ ବ୍ୟାକଟ୍ରେସ ସୃଷ୍ଟି କରିପାରିବ। କ୍ଷତି: ନଷ୍ଟ ପ୍ରଗ୍ରାମରୁ ସମସ୍ତ ତଥ୍ୟ କୋରଡମ୍ପ ଧାରଣ କରିଥାଏ, ଆପଣଙ୍କର ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ତଥ୍ୟକୁ ମଧ୍ଯ, ଯଦି ଥାଏ।</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="pa">ਕੋਰਡੰਪ ਨੂੰ ਸਰਵਰ ਤੇ ਅੱਪਲੋਡ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ, ਜੋ ਬੈਕਟਰੇਸ ਬਣਾਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ ਅਤੇ ਵਾਪਸ ਭੇਜਦੀ ਹੈ। Pros: ਡੀਬੱਗ-ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਡਾਊਨਲੋਡ ਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਕੋਈ ਲੋੜ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੈ। ਰੀਟਰੇਸ ਸਰਵਰ ਦਾ ਡੀਬੱਗ-ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਡਾਟਾਬੇਸ ਦੀ ਰੀਟਰੇਸ ਜਿਆਦਾ ਮੁਕੰਮਲ ਹੈ। ਰੀਟਰੇਸ ਸਰਵਰ ਵਧੀਆ ਬੈਕਟਰੇਸ ਬਣਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। Cons: ਕੋਰਡੰਪ ਜੋ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਅੱਪਲੋਡ ਕੀਤਾ ਹੈ ਉਸ ਵਿੱਚ ਕਰੈਸ਼ ਪਰੋਗਰਾਮ ਦੀ ਸਾਰਾ ਡਾਟਾ ਸ਼ਾਮਿਲ ਹੈ, ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਪਰਾਈਵੇਟ ਡਾਟੇ ਸਮੇਤ, ਜੇ ਕੋਈ ਹੈ।</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="pl">Wysyła zrzuty core do serwera, który tworzy wyjątek i go zwraca. Zalety: nie trzeba pobierać pakietów debuginfo. Baza danych pakietów debuginfo serwera ponownego śledzenia jest bardziej kompletna. Może on tworzyć lepsze wyjątki. Wady: wysyłane zrzuty core zawierają wszystkie dane programu, który uległ awarii, w tym potencjalnie prywatne dane.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="pt">Envia "coredump" para um servidor, que gera um ''backtrace'' e devolve-o. Vantagens: não precisa de transferências de "debuginfos". A base de dados de "debuginfos" do servidor "retrace" é mais completa. O servidor de "retrace" pode gerar melhores ''backtraces''. Desvantagens: o "coredump" que envia contém todos os dados do programa que crachou, incluindo, se existirem, os dados privados.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="pt_BR">Faz o upload do coredump a um servidor, que gera o backtrace e o retorna. Vantagens: sem necessidade de baixar o debuginfo. O banco de dados do servidor de retraçamento é mais completo. O servidor de retraçamento pode gerar backtraces melhores. Desvantagens: o coredump que você fez upload contém todos os dados do programa que travou, incluindo os dados privados, se houverem.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ru">Отправляет дамп памяти на сервер для генерации протокола сбоя. Достоинства: не требуется загружать debuginfo. База данных на отслеживающем сервере более подробная, поэтому сервер может создавать более точные отчёты. Недостатки: отправляемый дамп содержит все данные сбойной программы, в том числе и личные.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="sk">Nahrať coredump na server, ktorý vygeneruje a vráti backtrace. Výhody: nie je nutné sťahovať a inštalovať debuginfo balíčky. Databáza debuginfo balíkov Retrace serveru je obsiahlejšia, čo môže vplývať na výslednú kvalitu vygenerovaných backtrace. Nevýhody: coredump odoslaný na server obsahuje všetky dáta programu, ktorý spadol - môže obsahovať súkromné dáta.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="sq">Ngarkon coredump në një server, i cili gjeneron përgjurmues dhe e kthen atë. Avantazhe: nuk ka nevojë për shkarkimin e info rregullueseve. Serveri ripërshkrues i bazës së të dhënave tek info rregulluesi është më i kompletuar. Serveri ripërshkrimes mund të gjenerojë një përgjurmues më të mirë. Disavantazhe: ngarkimi i coredump përmban të gjithë të dhënat nga programi i përplasur, duke përfshirë të dhënat tuaja private, në qoftë se keni.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="sr">Шаље coredump на сервер, који ствара стабло позивања и враћа га. Предности: нема потребе за преузимањем debuginfo-а. База података debuginfo-а сервера за поновни траг је комплетнија. Сервер за поновни траг може створити боља стабла позивања. Мане: coredump који шаљете садржи све податке о срушеном програму, укључујући и ваше приватне податке, ако их има.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="sv">Skickar minnesdump till en server, vilken genererar ett stackspår och returnerar det.  Fördelar: inget behov av att hämta felsökningsinformation.  Spårningsserverns databas över felsökningsinformation är mer komplett.  Spårningsservern kan generera bättre stackspår.  Nackdelar: minnesdumpen du skickar innehåller all data från det kraschade programmet, inklusive eventuell personlig information.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ta">ஒரு சேவையகத்திற்கு coredump ஐ பதிவேற்றும், இது பின்தடமறிதலை உருவாக்கி வழங்குகிறது. நன்மைகள்: பிழைதிருத்த தகவல் பதிவிறக்கங்கள் தேவை இல்லை. மறுதடமறிதல் சேவையகத்தின் பிழைத்திருத்தத் தகவல் தரவுத்தளம் அதிக முழுமையாக உள்ளது. மறுதடமறிதல்சேவையகமானது மேலும் சிறப்பான பின் தடமறிதல்களை உருவாக்கலாம். குறைபாடுகள்: நீங்கள் பதிவேற்றும்கோர்டம்பில், உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவு ஏதேனும் இருப்பின் அவை உட்பட செயலிழந்த நிரலிலிருந்து கிடைக்கும் எல்லா தரவும் இருக்கும்.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="te">కోర్‌డంప్‌ను సర్వర్‌కు అప్‌లోడ్ చేయును, యిది బ్యాక్‌ట్రేస్‌ను సృష్టించి మరియు దానిని తిప్పియిచ్చును. లాభాలు: డీబగ్‌యిన్ఫో డౌన్‌లోడ్ చేయవలసిన అవసరం లేదు. రీట్రేస్ సర్వర్ యొక్క డీబగ్‌యిన్ఫోల డాటాబేస్ పూర్తిగా వుండును. రీట్రేస్ సర్వర్ మంచి బ్యాక్‌ట్రేస్‌లను జనియింపచేయగలదు. నష్టాలు: మీరు అప్‌లోడ్ చేసిన కోర్‌డంప్ క్రాష్‌డ్ ప్రోగ్రామ్‌నుండి మొత్తం డాటాను కలిగివుంటుంది, మీ వ్యక్తిగత డాటా యేదైనా వుంటే దానితో సహా.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="tr">Bellek dökümünü yığın geri izlemesi oluşturan ve geri döndüren bir sunucuya yükler. Artıları: debuginfo indirmelerine gerek yoktur. Retrace sunucusunun debuginfo veri tabanı daha eksiksizdir. Retrace sunucusu daha iyi yığın geri izlemeleri oluşturabilir. Eksileri: Yüklediğiniz bellek dökümü, varsa özel verileriniz de dahil olmak üzere, çöken programdaki tüm verileri içerir.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="uk">Вивантажує дамп ядра на сервер. Сервер створить дані зворотного трасування і поверне їх вам. Переваги: не потрібно встановлювати пакунки debuginfo. База даних пакунків debuginfo може бути повнішою за вашу. Сервер повторного трасування може отримати кращі дані зворотного трасування. Недоліки: дамп ядра, який буде вивантажено, міститиме всі дані з аварійної програми, зокрема конфіденційні дані, якщо такі там зберігалися.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="zh_CN">上传核心转储至服务器，由服务器生成回溯数据并返回。优点：无需下载 debuginfo；追溯服务器的 debuginfo 数据库更加完整；追溯服务器可以生成更好的回溯。缺点：您上传的核心转储包含崩溃程序的所有数据，如果有私人数据，也将会包含在其中。</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="zh_TW">Uploads coredump to a server, which generates backtrace and returns it. Pros: no need for debuginfo downloads. Retrace server's database of debuginfos is more complete. Retrace server may generate better backtraces. Cons: coredump you upload contains all the data from the crashed program, including your private data, if any.</long-description>
    <gui-review-elements>no</gui-review-elements>
    <sending-sensitive-data>yes</sending-sensitive-data>
    <options>
        <import-event-options event="report_Bugzilla"/>

        <option type="text" name="RETRACE_SERVER_URI">
           <label>Retrace server URI</label>
           <label xml:lang="cs">URI stopovacího serveru</label>
           <label xml:lang="da">Sporingsserverens URI</label>
           <label xml:lang="de">URI des Retrace-Servers</label>
           <label xml:lang="es">URL del servidor de rastreo</label>
           <label xml:lang="fi">Uudelleenjäljityspalvelimen URI</label>
           <label xml:lang="fr">URI du serveur retrace</label>
           <label xml:lang="hu">Nyomkövetési kiszolgáló URI</label>
           <label xml:lang="nl">Retrace-server URI</label>
           <label xml:lang="pl">Adres URI serwera ponownego śledzenia</label>
           <label xml:lang="pt">URI do servidor da traçagem</label>
           <label xml:lang="pt_BR">URI do servidor de retraçamento</label>
           <label xml:lang="ru">URI отслеживающего сервера</label>
           <label xml:lang="sv">Spårningsserver-URI</label>
           <label xml:lang="tr">Retrace server URI'si</label>
           <label xml:lang="uk">Адреса сервера повторного трасування</label>
           <label xml:lang="zh_CN">追溯服务器 URI</label>
           <default-value>https://retrace.fedoraproject.org</default-value>
           <allow-empty>no</allow-empty>
           <description>Address of the retrace server</description>
           <description xml:lang="as">ৰিট্ৰেইচ চাৰ্ভাৰৰ ঠিকনা</description>
           <description xml:lang="bg">Адрес на сървър за обратно проследяване</description>
           <description xml:lang="bn">retrace সার্ভারের ঠিকানা</description>
           <description xml:lang="bn_IN">retrace সার্ভারের ঠিকানা</description>
           <description xml:lang="bs">Adresa retrace servera</description>
           <description xml:lang="ca">Adreça del servidor de retraçat</description>
           <description xml:lang="cs">Adresa retrace serveru</description>
           <description xml:lang="da">Adresse på sporingsserveren</description>
           <description xml:lang="de">Adresse des Retrace-Servers</description>
           <description xml:lang="el">Διεύθυνση του εξυπηρετητή επανανίχνευσης</description>
           <description xml:lang="en_GB">Address of the retrace server</description>
           <description xml:lang="es">Dirección del servidor retrace</description>
           <description xml:lang="et">Taasjälituse serveri aadress</description>
           <description xml:lang="fi">Retrace-palvelimen osoite</description>
           <description xml:lang="fr">Adresse du serveur retrace</description>
           <description xml:lang="gu">રિટ્રેસ સર્વરનું સરનામું</description>
           <description xml:lang="he">כתובת שרת ה־retrace</description>
           <description xml:lang="hi">रिट्रेस सर्वर का पता</description>
           <description xml:lang="hu">A nyomkövetési kiszolgáló címe</description>
           <description xml:lang="ia">Adresse del servitor de retraciamento</description>
           <description xml:lang="id">Alamat dari retrace server</description>
           <description xml:lang="it">Indirizzo del Retrace server</description>
           <description xml:lang="ja">リトレースサーバーのアドレス</description>
           <description xml:lang="kn">ರಿಟ್ರೇಸ್ ಪೂರೈಕೆಗಣಕದ ವಿಳಾಸ</description>
           <description xml:lang="ko">Retrace 서버 주소 </description>
           <description xml:lang="lt">Pertrasavimo serverio adresas</description>
           <description xml:lang="ml">റീട്രെയിസ് സര്‍വറിന്റെ വിലാസം</description>
           <description xml:lang="mr">रिट्रेस सर्व्हरचा पत्ता</description>
           <description xml:lang="nl">Adres van de retrace-server</description>
           <description xml:lang="or">ଅନୁସନ୍ଧାନ ସର୍ଭର ଠିକଣା</description>
           <description xml:lang="pa">ਰੀਟਰੇਸ ਸਰਵਰ ਦਾ ਐਡਰੈੱਸ</description>
           <description xml:lang="pl">Adres serwera ponownego śledzenia</description>
           <description xml:lang="pt">Endereço do servidor retrace</description>
           <description xml:lang="pt_BR">Endereço do servidor de retraçamento</description>
           <description xml:lang="ru">Адрес отслеживающего сервера</description>
           <description xml:lang="sk">Adresa retrace serveru</description>
           <description xml:lang="sq">Adresa e serverit retrace</description>
           <description xml:lang="sr">Адреса сервера поновног трага</description>
           <description xml:lang="sv">Adress till spårningsservern</description>
           <description xml:lang="ta">மறுதடமறிதல் சேவையகத்தின் முகவரி</description>
           <description xml:lang="te">రిట్రేస్ సర్వర్ యొక్క చిరునామా</description>
           <description xml:lang="tr">Retrace sunucusunun adresi</description>
           <description xml:lang="uk">Адреса сервера повторного трасування</description>
           <description xml:lang="zh_CN">追溯服务器地址</description>
           <description xml:lang="zh_TW">追溯伺服器的位址</description>
       </option>
       <option type="text" name="RETRACE_SERVER_INSECURE">
           <label>Insecure</label>
           <label xml:lang="as">অসুৰক্ষিত</label>
           <label xml:lang="bg">Незащитена</label>
           <label xml:lang="bn">অসুরক্ষিত</label>
           <label xml:lang="bn_IN">অসুরক্ষিত</label>
           <label xml:lang="ca">Insegur</label>
           <label xml:lang="cs">Nezabezpečený</label>
           <label xml:lang="da">Usikker</label>
           <label xml:lang="de">Unsicher</label>
           <label xml:lang="en_GB">Insecure</label>
           <label xml:lang="es">Inseguro</label>
           <label xml:lang="et">Ebaturvaline</label>
           <label xml:lang="fi">Suojaamaton</label>
           <label xml:lang="fr">Non-sécurisée</label>
           <label xml:lang="gl">Inseguro</label>
           <label xml:lang="gu">અસુરક્ષિત</label>
           <label xml:lang="he">בלתי מאובטח</label>
           <label xml:lang="hi">असुरक्षित </label>
           <label xml:lang="hu">Nem biztonságos</label>
           <label xml:lang="id">Tidak aman</label>
           <label xml:lang="it">Non sicura</label>
           <label xml:lang="ja">安全ではありません</label>
           <label xml:lang="kn">ಅಸುರಕ್ಷಿತ</label>
           <label xml:lang="ko">비보안 </label>
           <label xml:lang="lt">Nesaugus</label>
           <label xml:lang="lv">Nedrošs</label>
           <label xml:lang="ml">അസുരക്ഷിതം</label>
           <label xml:lang="mr">असुरक्षित</label>
           <label xml:lang="nb">Usikker</label>
           <label xml:lang="nl">Onveilig</label>
           <label xml:lang="or">ଅସୁରକ୍ଷିତ</label>
           <label xml:lang="pa">ਅਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ</label>
           <label xml:lang="pl">Niezabezpieczone</label>
           <label xml:lang="pt">Inseguro</label>
           <label xml:lang="pt_BR">Inseguro</label>
           <label xml:lang="ru">Незащищенное</label>
           <label xml:lang="sk">Nezabezpečené</label>
           <label xml:lang="sq">E pasigurtë</label>
           <label xml:lang="sr">Несигурно</label>
           <label xml:lang="sv">Osäker</label>
           <label xml:lang="ta">பாதுகாப்பற்ற</label>
           <label xml:lang="te">సురక్షితంకాని</label>
           <label xml:lang="tr">Güvensiz</label>
           <label xml:lang="uk">Незахищене</label>
           <label xml:lang="zh_CN">不安全</label>
           <label xml:lang="zh_TW">不安全</label>
           <allow-empty>yes</allow-empty>
           <description>Whether or not to use insecure connection</description>
           <description xml:lang="as">অসুৰক্ষিত সংযোগ ব্যৱহাৰ কৰা হব নে</description>
           <description xml:lang="bg">Да ползвам ли или не незащитена връзка</description>
           <description xml:lang="bn">অসুরক্ষিত সংযোগ ব্যবহার করা হবে কি না</description>
           <description xml:lang="bn_IN">অসুরক্ষিত সংযোগ ব্যবহার করা হবে কি না</description>
           <description xml:lang="ca">Utilitzar o no utilitzar la connexió insegura</description>
           <description xml:lang="cs">Použít nezabezpečeného připojení?</description>
           <description xml:lang="da">Hvorvidt der skal bruges usikker forbindelse</description>
           <description xml:lang="de">Ob eine unsichere Verbindung verwendet werden soll</description>
           <description xml:lang="en_GB">Whether or not to use insecure connection</description>
           <description xml:lang="es">Utilizar o no una conexión insegura</description>
           <description xml:lang="et">Kas kasutada või mitte ebaturvalist ühendust</description>
           <description xml:lang="fi">Käytetäänkö suojaamatonta yhteyttä</description>
           <description xml:lang="fr">Utiliser ou non une connexion non-sécurisée</description>
           <description xml:lang="fur">Indiche se doprâ o mancul lis conessions no siguris</description>
           <description xml:lang="gl">Se empregar ou non unha conexión insegura</description>
           <description xml:lang="gu">શું અસુરક્ષિત જોડાણને વાપરવું કે નહિં</description>
           <description xml:lang="he">האם להשתמש בחיבור בלתי מאובטח</description>
           <description xml:lang="hi">क्या असुरक्षित कनेक्शन का उपयोग करना है या नहीं</description>
           <description xml:lang="hu">Használjon-e nem biztonságos kapcsolatot</description>
           <description xml:lang="it">Usare, o meno, una connessione non sicura</description>
           <description xml:lang="ja">安全ではない接続を使用する、または使用しない</description>
           <description xml:lang="kn">ಅಸುರಕ್ಷಿತ ಸಂಪರ್ಕವನ್ನು ಬಳಸಬೇಕೆ ಅಥವ ಬೇಡವೆ</description>
           <description xml:lang="ko">비보안 연결을 사용할 지에 대한 여부 </description>
           <description xml:lang="lt">Ar naudoti nesaugų ryšį</description>
           <description xml:lang="ml">അസുരക്ഷിതമായ കണക്ഷന്‍ ഉപയോഗിയ്ക്കണമോ വേണ്ടേ എന്നു്</description>
           <description xml:lang="mr">असुरक्षित जोडणीचा वापर करायचा किंवा नाही</description>
           <description xml:lang="nl">De onveilige verbinding wel of niet gebruiken</description>
           <description xml:lang="or">ଅସୁରକ୍ଷିତ ସଂଯୋଗକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରିବା ଉଚିତ କି ନୁହଁ</description>
           <description xml:lang="pa">ਅਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਕੁਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਵਰਤਣਾ ਹੈ ਜਾਂ ਨਹੀਂ</description>
           <description xml:lang="pl">Określa, czy używać niezabezpieczonego połączenia</description>
           <description xml:lang="pt">Utilizar ou não uma ligação insegura</description>
           <description xml:lang="pt_BR">Usar ou não conexão insegura</description>
           <description xml:lang="ru">Использование незащищенного подключения</description>
           <description xml:lang="sk">Použiť nezabezpečené pripojenie alebo nie</description>
           <description xml:lang="sq">Të përdoret apo jo lidhja e pasigurtë</description>
           <description xml:lang="sr">Да ли да користи несигурну везу или не</description>
           <description xml:lang="sv">Huruvida en osäker förbindelse skall användas eller ej</description>
           <description xml:lang="ta">பாதுகாப்பாற்ற இணைப்பை பயன்படுத்தவா அல்லது வேண்டாமா</description>
           <description xml:lang="te">సురక్షితం కాని అనుసంధానంను వుపయోగించాలా వద్దా</description>
           <description xml:lang="tr">Güvenli olmayan bağlantı kullanılıp kullanılmayacağı</description>
           <description xml:lang="uk">Визначає, чи можна використовувати незахищене з’єднання</description>
           <description xml:lang="zh_CN">是否使用不安全连接</description>
           <description xml:lang="zh_TW">是否使用不安全的連線</description>
           <note-html>Write "insecure" to allow SSL to use self-signed or expired certificates.</note-html>
       </option>

    </options>
</event>