<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<event>
    <name>Analyze C/C++ Crash</name>
    <description>Send core dump to remote retrace server for analysis or perform local analysis if the remote analysis fails</description>
    <description xml:lang="as">বিশ্লেষণৰ বাবে দূৰৱৰ্তী ৰিট্ৰেইচ চাৰ্ভাৰলে কেন্দ্ৰীয় ডাম্প পঠাওক অথবা দূৰৱৰ্তী বিশ্লেষণ ব্যৰ্থ হলে স্থানীয় বিশ্লেষণ পৰিৱেশন কৰক</description>
    <description xml:lang="bn_IN">বিশ্লেষণের জন্য দূরবর্তী retrace সার্ভারের মধ্যে কোর-ডাম্প পাঠানো হবে অথবা দূরবর্তী বিশ্লেষণ বিফল হলে স্থানীয় বিশ্লেষণ সঞ্চালিত হবে</description>
    <description xml:lang="ca">Envia el bolc de la memòria a un servidor remot de retraçat per a l'anàlisi o per a la realització de l'anàlisi local si es produeix un error en el servidor remot de l'anàlisi</description>
    <description xml:lang="cs">Odešle obraz paměti k analýze na vzdálený retrace server, nebo spustí lokální analýzu pokud vzdálená analýza selže</description>
    <description xml:lang="da">Send kernedump til fjern-sporingsserver til analyse eller udfør lokal analyse hvis fjern-analyse ikke lykkedes</description>
    <description xml:lang="de">Speicherauszug an entfernten Retrace-Server zur Untersuchung senden oder lokale Analyse durchführen, falls die entfernte Analyse fehlschlägt</description>
    <description xml:lang="en_GB">Send core dump to remote retrace server for analysis or perform local analysis if the remote analysis fails</description>
    <description xml:lang="es">Enviar el volcado de memoria al servidor retrace remoto para su análisis o ejecutar un análisis local si falla el análisis remoto</description>
    <description xml:lang="fr">Envoyer le vidage mémoire au serveur retrace distant pour analyse ou effectuer une analyse locale si l’analyse distante échoue</description>
    <description xml:lang="gl">Enviar o envorcado do core ao servidor remoto de retrazados para analizar ou realizar unha análise local se a análise remota falla</description>
    <description xml:lang="gu">સ્થાનિક વિશ્ર્લેષણને ચલાવવા અથવા વિશ્ર્લેષણ માટે દૂરસ્થ રિટ્રેસ સર્વરમાં કૉર ડમ્પ મોકલો જો દૂરસ્થ વિશ્ર્લેષણ નિષ્ફળ જાય</description>
    <description xml:lang="hi">दूरस्थ रिट्रेस सर्वर में कोर डंप भेजें यदि दूरस्थ विश्लेषण विफल रहता है तो विश्लेषण या स्थानीय विश्लेषण के लिए।</description>
    <description xml:lang="hu">Küldje el az összeomlási adatokat a távoli nyomkövető kiszolgálónak elemzésre, vagy végezze el helyben az elemzést, ha a távoli folyamat meghiúsulna</description>
    <description xml:lang="it">Invia il core dump al retrace server remoto per l'analisi oppure effettua l'analisi localmente se quella remota fallisce</description>
    <description xml:lang="ja">分析のためコアダンプをリモートのリトレースサーバーに送信するか、リモートの分析に失敗した場合はローカルの分析を行ないます</description>
    <description xml:lang="kn">ಕೋರ್ ಡಂಪ್ ಅನ್ನು ವಿಶ್ಲೇಷಣೆಗಾಗಿ ದೂರಸ್ಥ ರಿಟ್ರೇಸ್ ಪೂರೈಕೆಗಣಕಕ್ಕೆ ಕಳುಹಿಸು ಅಥವ ದೂರಸ್ಥ ವಿಶ್ಲೇಷಣೆಯು ವಿಫಲಗೊಂಡಲ್ಲಿ ಸ್ಥಳೀಯ ವಿಶ್ಲೇಷಣೆಯನ್ನು ನಿರ್ವಹಿಸು</description>
    <description xml:lang="ko">원격 분석을 실패하는 경우 로컬 분석을 수행하기 위해 원격 역추적 서버에 코어 덤프를 전송합니다 </description>
    <description xml:lang="lt">Siųsti pagrindo išklotinę į nutolusį pertrasavimo serverį analizei arba atlikti vietinę analizę, jei nuotolinė analizė nepavyksta</description>
    <description xml:lang="ml">നിരീക്ഷിയ്ക്കുന്നതിനായി റിമോട്ട് റീട്രെയിസ് സര്‍വറിലേക്കു് കോര്‍ ഡംപ് അയയ്ക്കുക അല്ലെങ്കില്‍ ഇതു് പരാജപ്പെട്ടാല്‍, നിങ്ങളുടെ സിസ്റ്റത്തിലുള്ള നിരീക്ഷണം നടപ്പിലാക്കുക</description>
    <description xml:lang="mr">रिमोट विश्लेषण अपयशी ठरल्यास विश्लेषण किंवा स्थानीय विश्लेषण सुरू करण्यासाठी कोर डम्पला रिमोट रिट्रेस् सर्व्हरकरीता पाठवा</description>
    <description xml:lang="nl">Verstuur de coredump naar de retrace-server op afstand voor analyse, of voer lokale analyse uit indien de analyse op afstand mislukt</description>
    <description xml:lang="or">ସୁଦୂର ଅନୁସନ୍ଧାନ ସର୍ଭର ପାଖକୁ ବିଶ୍ଳେଷଣ ପାଇଁ କୋରଡମ୍ପ ପଠାନ୍ତୁ ଅଥବା ସୁଦୂର ବିଶ୍ଳେଷଣ ବିଫଳ ହେଲେ ସ୍ଥାନୀୟ ବିଶ୍ଳେଷଣ କରନ୍ତୁ</description>
    <description xml:lang="pa">ਕੋਰ ਡੰਪ ਨੂੰ ਰਿਮੋਟ ਸਰਵਰ ਤੇ ਜਾਂਚ ਲਈ ਭੇਜੋ</description>
    <description xml:lang="pl">Wysyła zrzut core do serwera ponownego śledzenia w celu wykonania analizy lub wykonuje analizę lokalnie, jeśli zdalna analiza się nie powiedzie</description>
    <description xml:lang="pt_BR">Enviar o dump para o servidor retrace remoto para análise ou realizar análises locais, caso a análise remota falhar</description>
    <description xml:lang="ru">Передача дампа памяти удалённому серверу для анализа. В случае неудачи выполнить анализ локально</description>
    <description xml:lang="sk">Odoslať výpis jadra na analýzu do vzdialeného servera retrace, alebo vykonať lokálnu analýzu, ak zlyhá vzdialená analýza.</description>
    <description xml:lang="sq">Dërgo core dump në serverin e largët retrace për analizim lokal nëse analizimi i largët dështon</description>
    <description xml:lang="sr">Пошаљи coredump на удаљени сервер за поновни траг на анализу или изврши локалну анализу ако удаљена анализа није успешна</description>
    <description xml:lang="sv">Skicka en minnesdump till fjärrspårservern för analys eller analysera lokalt om fjärranalysen inte fungerar.</description>
    <description xml:lang="ta">கோர் டம்ப்பை பகுப்பாய்வுக்காக தொலைநிலை ரிடிரேஸ் சேவையகத்திற்கு அனுப்பவும் அல்லது தொலைநிலை பகுப்பாய்வு தோல்வியடைந்தால் கணினிக்குள்ளான பகுப்பாய்வைச் செய்யவும்</description>
    <description xml:lang="te">కోర్ డంప్‌ను దూరస్థ రీట్రేస్ సేవికకు పంపి విశ్లేషణ జరుపుము లేదా దూరస్థ విశ్లేషణ విఫలమైతే స్థానిక విశ్లేషమ జరపండి</description>
    <description xml:lang="tr">İncelemek için uzak retrace sunucusuna bellek dökümü gönderin veya uzaktan inceleme başarısız olursa yerel inceleme gerçekleştirin</description>
    <description xml:lang="uk">Надіслати дамп ядра на віддалений сервер повторного трасування для аналізу або виконати локальний аналіз, якщо виконати віддалений аналіз не вдасться</description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_CN">向远程回溯服务器发送核心转储供于分析，或在远程分析失败时执行本地分析</description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_TW">傳送核心傾印至遠端追溯伺服器來分析，若遠端分析失敗或可執行本地端分析</description>
    <long-description>Uploads coredump to a server, which generates backtrace and returns it. If user doesn't want to upload his coredump to anywhere the event performs local analysis. Local analysis is run event if remote analysis fails. Pros: no need for debuginfo downloads. Retrace server's database of debuginfos is more complete. Retrace server may generate better backtraces. Cons: coredump you upload contains all the data from the crashed program, including your private data, if any.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ca">Puja el bolc de la memòria a un servidor que genera una traça inversa i la retorna. Si l'usuari no vol pujar el seu bolc de la memòria enlloc, l'esdeveniment realitza localment l'anàlisi. L'anàlisi local s'executa si falla l'anàlisi remota. Pros: no hi ha la necessitat de baixar els debuginfo. La base de dades dels debuginfo del servidor de retraçat és més completa. El servidor de retraçat pot generar millor les traces inverses. Cons: el bolc de la memòria que pugeu conté totes les dades del programa que ha tingut pana, que inclouen les vostres dades privades, si fos el cas.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="cs">Nahrává coredump na server, který vygeneruje backtrace a vrátí ho. Nechce-li uživatel coredump nikam nahrávat, provede se lokální analýza. Lokální analýza se provedete také, když vzdálená analýza selže. Výhody: není potřeba stahovat debuginfo. Databáze debuginfo na retrace serveru je kompletnější. Retrace server může generovat lepší backtracy. Nevýhody: coredump, který odesíláte, obsahuje všechny data ze spadnutého programu včetně soukromých, pokud tam nějaká jsou.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="da">Uploader kernedump til en server, som genererer backtracet og returnerer det. Hvis brugeren ikke vil uploade sin kernedump nogen steder udfører hændelsen lokal analyse. Lokal analyse kører hændelsen hvis fjern-analyse ikke lykkes. Fordele: ingen behov til at downloade fejlsøgningsinfo. Retraceserverens database over fejlsøgningsinformationer er mere komplet. Retraceserveren genererer muligvis bedre backtraces. Ulemper: kernedumpninger som du uploader indeholder alle data fra det nedbrudte program, inklusiv dine private data, hvis de er tilstede.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="de">Überträgt den Speicherauszug an einen Retrace-Server, der eine Ablaufverfolgung erstellt und zurücksendet. Falls der Anwender diese Daten nicht senden will, wird eine lokale Analyse erstellt. Die Debuginfo-Datenbank des Retrace-Servers ist in der Regel vollständiger. Dagegen spricht, dass der zu übertragende Speicherauszug alle Daten des abgestürzten Programms enthält, eventuell auch vertrauliche Daten.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="es">Sube el volcado de memoria a un servidor, que generará un trazado y lo devolverá. Si el usuario no desea subir el volcado a ningún sitio, se llevará a cabo un análisis local. El análisis local es ejecutado si el análisis remoto falla. Pros: no son necesarias las descargas de información de depuración. La base de datos de información de depuración del servidor Retrace es más completa. El servidor Retrace puede generar mejores trazas de vuelta. Contras: el archivo de volcado que va a subir contiene todos los datos del programa que ha fallado, incluidos datos privados si los hubiera.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="fr">Téléverse le vidage mémoire sur un serveur, qui génère une trace arrière et la retourne. Si l’utilisateur ne souhaite pas téléverser le vidage mémoire où que ce soit, l’évènement effectuera une analyse locale. L’analyse locale est exécutée même si l’analyse distante échoue. Avantages : il n’est pas nécessaire d’effectuer des téléchargements de fichiers debuginfo. La base de données du serveur Retrace des debuginfos est plus complète. Le serveur Retrace peut générer de meilleures traces arrière. Inconvénients : les vidages mémoire téléchargés contiennent toutes les données du programme en panne, y compris les données privées s’il y en a.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="hu">Feltölti az összeomlási adatokat egy kiszolgálónak, amely előállítja a nyomkövetést, és visszaadja azt. Ha a felhasználó nem akarja feltölteni az összeomlási adatait, akkor helyben lesz elemezve. A helyi elemzést akkor is lefut, ha a távoli elemzés meghiúsult. Előnyök: nincs szükség debuginfo csomagok letöltésére. A nyomkövetési kiszolgáló debuginfo adatai teljesebbek. A nyomkövetési kiszolgáló jobb nyomkövetést adhat vissza. Hátrányok: az összeomlási adatok tartalmazzák az összeomlott program összes adatát, a személyes adatait is.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="it">Carica il coredump sul server, generando un backtrace e successivamente ritornandolo. Se l'utente non vuole inviare il suo coredump all'esterno, viene effettuata una analisi locale. La analisi locale è usata anche quando quella remota fallisce. Pro: non c'è bisogno di scaricare le informazioni di debug. Il database delle informazioni di debug sul retrace server è più completo. Il retrace server può generare backtrace migliori. Contro: il coredump da caricare contiene tutti i dati del programma, incluso dati privati quando presenti.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ja">コアダンプをサーバーにアップロードします。これによりバックトレースが生成され返されます。コアダンプをどこにもアップロードしたくない場合、 ローカルの分析が行われます。リモートの分析に失敗した場合にもローカルの分析が実行されます。debuginfo をダウンロードする必要がない点が利点となります。リトレースサーバーの debaguinfo データベースの方がより完全なデータベースとなるため、リトレースサーバーの方がより適切なバックトレースを生成することができます。一方、アップロードするコアダンプにはクラッシュしたプログラムの全データが含まれるため、プライベートデータがある場合には、そのデータも含まれることになります。</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="lt">Nusiunčia išklotinę į serverį, kuris sugeneruoja ir grąžina pėdsaką. Jei naudotojas nenori nusiųsti savo išklotinės, įvykis atlieka vietinę analizę. Vietinė analizė vykdoma, net jei nuotolinė analizė nepavyksta. Privalumai: nereikia parsisiųsti derinimo informacijos. Trasavimo serverio derinimo informacijos duomenų bazė yra pilnesnė. Trūkumai: siunčiamoje išklotinėje yra visi lūžusios programos duomenys, tarp kurių gali būti ir privačių duomenų.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="nl">Uploadt de coredump naar een server, die de backtrace genereert en deze terugstuurt. Als de gebruiker zijn coredump nergens naar toe wil uploaden dan zal het voorval lokale analyse uitvoeren. Lokale analyse wordt uitgevoerd als analyse op afstand mislukt. Voordelen: er wordt geen debuginfo gedownload. De database van de retrace-server is completer. De retrace-server kan betere backtraces aanmaken. Nadelen: de coredump die je uploadt bevat alle data van het gecrashte programma, mogelijk inclusief persoonlijke data.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="pl">Wysyła zrzut core do serwera, który tworzy wyjątek i go zwraca. Jeśli użytkownik nie chce wysyłać swojego zrzutu, to zdarzenie wykonuje analizę lokalną. Lokalna analiza jest wykonywana także wtedy, gdy zdalna analiza się nie powiedzie. Zalety: nie trzeba pobierać pakietów debuginfo. Baza danych pakietów debuginfo serwera ponownego śledzenia jest bardziej kompletna. Może on tworzyć lepsze wyjątki. Wady: wysyłane zrzuty core zawierają wszystkie dane programu, który uległ awarii, w tym potencjalnie prywatne dane.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="pt_BR">Carrega o coredump em um servidor, que gera o backtrace e retorna-o. Se o usuário não desejar carregar seu coredump para qualquer lugar que o evento realize análise local. A análise local é executada se a análise remota falhar. Prós: não é necessário fazer downloads de debuginfo. O banco de dados do servidor Retrace de debuginfos é mais completo. O Servidor Retrace pode gerar melhores backtraces. Contras: o coredump que você carrega contém todos os dados do programa de travamento, incluindo seus dados pessoais, caso haja algum.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ru">Отправляет дамп памяти на сервер для создания протокола сбоя. По желанию анализ события может быть произведен локально. Локальный анализ также будет выполнен, даже если не удастся выполнить его удаленно. Достоинства: не требуется загружать debuginfo. База данных на отслеживающем сервере более полная, поэтому сервер может создавать более точные отчеты. Недостатки: отправляемый дамп содержит все данные сбойной программы, в том числе и конфиденциальные.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="sq">Ngarkon coredump në një server, i cili gjeneron përgjurmues dhe e kthen atë. Në qoftë se përdoruesi nuk do të ngarkoj coredump të tij gjithandej eventi do të performohet lokalisht. Analiza lokale është një event i vazhdueshëm nëse analiza e largët dështon. Avantazhe: nuk ka nevojë për shkarkimin e info rregullueseve. Serveri ripërshkrues i bazës së të dhënave tek info rregulluesi është më i kompletuar. Serveri ripërshkrimes mund të gjenerojë një përgjuues më të mirë. Disavantazhe: ngarkimi i coredump përmban të gjithë të dhënat nga programi i përplasur, duke përfshirë të dhënat tuaja private, në qoftë se keni.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="sr">Шаље coredump на сервер, који ствара стабло позивања и враћа га. Ако корисник не жели да пошаље свој coredump нигде овај догађај ће извршити локалну анализу. Локална анализа се извршава и у случају да удаљена анализа није успешна. Предности: нема потребе за преузимањем debuginfo-а. База података debuginfo-а сервера за поновни траг је комплетнија. Сервер за поновни траг може створити боља стабла позивања. Мане: coredump који шаљете садржи све податке о срушеном програму, укључујући и ваше приватне податке, ако их има.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="sv">Skickar en minnesutskrift till en server, som genererar ett stackspår och returnerar det.  Om användaren inte vill skicka sin minnesutskrift någonstans utförs lokal analys av händelsen.  Lokal analys görs av händelsen om fjärranalysen misslyckas.  Fördelar: inget behov att hämta felsökningsinformation.  Spårningsserverns databas över felsökningsinformation är mer komplett.  Spårningsservern kan generera bättre stackspår.  Nackdelar: minnesutskrifter du skickar innehåller all data från det kraschade programmet, inklusive dina privata data om det finns några.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="tr">Bellek dökümünü sunucuya yükler, bu da yığın geri izlemesi oluşturur ve onu döndürür. Kullanıcı, bellek dökümünü herhangi bir yere yüklemek istemiyorsa, olay yerel inceleme gerçekleştirir. Uzaktan inceleme başarısız olsa bile yerel inceleme çalıştırılır. Artıları: debuginfo indirme işlemine gerek yoktur. Retrace sunucusunun debuginfo veri tabanı daha eksiksizdir. Retrace sunucusu daha iyi yığın geri izlemesi oluşturabilir. Eksileri: yüklediğiniz bellek dökümü, varsa özel verileriniz de dahil olmak üzere, çöken programdaki tüm verileri içerir.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="uk">Вивантажує дамп ядра на сервер, який створює дані зворотнього трасування і повертає їх на ваш комп’ютер. Якщо користувач не бажає вивантажувати дамп ядра, буде виконано локальний аналіз події. Локальний аналіз також буде виконано, якщо не вдасться виконати аналіз на віддаленому сервері. Переваги: не потрібно отримувати і встановлювати діагностичні пакунки, база діагностичних даних на сервері є повнішою за вашу. Сервер зворотного трасування може створити кращу картину для зворотного трасування. Недоліки: вивантажені вами дані дампу ядра можуть містити всі дані з програми, роботу якої було завершено у аварійному режимі, зокрема конфіденційні для вас дані.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="zh_CN">上传核心转储至服务器，由服务器生成并返回回溯结果。如果用户不想上传核心转储，也可以执行本地分析。如果远程分析失败本地分析会运行事件。优点：无需下载 debuginfo 软件包；追溯服务器的 debuginfo 数据库更加完整；追溯服务器可以生成更好的回溯。缺点：您上传的核心转储包含崩溃程序的所有数据，如果有私人数据，也将会包含在其中。</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="zh_TW">上傳核心傾印資料至伺服器，該伺服器會產生回溯資料並回傳。如果使用者此刻不想上傳核心傾印資料至其他地方，事件會改以本地端分析執行。優點：不需要下載 debuginfo 軟體包、追溯伺服器資料庫中的 debuginfo 比較完整、追溯伺服器可能會產生比較良好的回溯資料。缺點：您需要上傳核心傾印檔案，該檔案包含崩潰程式的所有資料，包括您的私人資料（如果有的話）。</long-description>
    <gui-review-elements>no</gui-review-elements>

    
    <sending-sensitive-data>no</sending-sensitive-data>

    <options>
        <import-event-options event="analyze_RetraceServer"/>
    </options>
</event>